- 喂 - 嘿 你在干嘛?
- Hello. - Hey, what're you doing?
噢 嗨
Oh, hi.
- 你在睡觉? - 没有
- Are you sleeping? - No.
- 噢 听到是我打来 你不高兴 - 没有 我很高兴
- Oh, you're not happy to hear from me. - No, I'm glad you called.
我想见你
I wanna see you.
什么 现在?
What, now?
- 对 现在 - 你在哪?
- Yes, now. - Where are you?
老地方
Same place as before.
Peabody
Peabody.
- 你确定你不是在睡觉? - 不 不 我醒着呢
- Are you sure you're not sleeping? - No, no, I was up.
你骗人 来吧 快过来
You liar. Come on, get your ass over here.
好 行了 你说了算
Yeah, okay. I mean, yeah, what the hell.
- 房号210 - 好的
- Room 210. - Fine.
- Sean Seanie - 怎么了?
- Sean, Seanie. - What?
我出去见个朋友
I have to go out and see  a friend for a little bit.
大概1 2个小时 行吗?
I'll be gone for an hour or two, okay?
我把手机号写在纸上
I put my cell phone on this slip of paper.
我放在上面的架子 行吗?
I'll put it on that top shelf, okay?
我刚说了什么?
What did I just say?
你要出去见个朋友 你号码放在上面的架子
You're going out to see a friend and your number's on the top shelf.
好样的
Attaboy.
克里早前有机会充分利用就业和经济问题
The Kerry camp had an early opportunity to capitalize on jobs and the economy...
从中获利 把总统拉下水
as an issue, and tag the President with it.
选举前的民调显示
The pre-election polls show  that a significant number...
大部分未有立场又易说服的选民认为
of undecided and persuadable voters...
克里一方提供的就业机会 比布什多
thought Kerry over Bush offered a better chance for jobs.
就业或许是个重要问题 Kate...
Jobs may have been a marginal issue, Kate...
在部分工业衰退地带 可称作是战场
in some of the Rust Belt battleground states.
不过 根本上 这是一次关于乔治·W·布什
But, ultimately, this was a referendum on the leadership of George W. Bush...
发动反恐战争和伊拉克战争的公民投票
on the war against terror  and the war in Iraq.
你满嘴胡话
You're so full of shit.
共和党的州里只有经济重要
Nothing mattered in the red  states but the economy.
我已经说了好几个月
I've been saying that for months.
嘿 我今晚没有让你走人啊 我明天没事
Hey, I'm not tossing you so quick tonight. I got nothing to do tomorrow.
我自己赶自己走啦
Well, I'm tossing myself.
我要回家了
I gotta get home.
你知道吗 我不是说这样不开心
You know what, not that this wasn't fun...
但先吃晚餐比较好 晚餐 看电影
but it might be nice to have dinner first. Dinner and a movie.
- 我到巴尔的摩的时候已经晚了 - 不 我说的是下次
- I got to Baltimore late. - No, I'm saying next time.
先聊聊天 然后狠狠操一把 对我这样的人 这样会不一样的
We talk some, then we fuck our brains out. It's different for girls like me.
要抱抱么 McNulty?
You need to be cuddled, McNulty?
不要 但我们得约会 感觉这样 自己像嫖客
No, but we make a date, I don't feel like I have to charge by the hour.
约会啊?
A date, huh?
我会打电话给你
I'll call you.
白天的时候
In the daytime.
我们都可以同意 这个对外政策
I think we can all agree that  foreign policy and...
当美国遭遇珍珠港袭击时...
while the United States was reeling from the attack on Pearl Harbor...
神奇的木头雕刻...
wonders of wood carving...
在会议上 他用美国国旗包住自己 头也不回
He wrapped himself in the American flag at the convention and never looked back.
别这样 Kate 这太刻薄了 不是吗?
Come on, Kate, that's a little  harsh, don't you think?
不 我是认真的
No, I don't, I'm serious.
我觉得也是他幕后智囊团出的主意
And I think it was great  strategy by his handlers, too.
你不也觉得当克里开始行动... 他在民主党全国代表大会
You don't think that when John Kerry kicked off... In his acceptance speech...
发表赞同演讲说 "我追随祖国国旗"时
at the Democratic National Convention he said, "I'm here under Old Glory"...
他也想要用国旗包住自己来着?
that he wasn't trying to wrap  himself in the flag, too?
不 我不觉得他要用国旗包自己
No, I don't think he was trying  to wrap himself in the flag.
我觉得他是要维护那些摇摆州的人民
I think he was trying to defend the people in the battleground states.
那些...
The ones who...
1942年 美国第一海军战队闯入瓜达康纳尔岛岸
1942, the US 1st Marine Division stormed the shore at Guadalcanal...
几乎全部占领Lunga Point飞机场
seizing a nearly complete  airfield at Lunga Point...
将其重命名为Henderson Field
which was renamed Henderson Field...
还有一个Tulagi附近的停泊处
and an anchorage at nearby Tulagi...
也就是日后的Iron Bottom Sound
that would later be known  as Iron Bottom Sound...
名字由来是在战争中 许多船只在此沉没
because of the number  of ships sunk there in battle.
登陆第一天 接近1万1千名陆战队队员
The landings of the first day put nearly 11,000 Marines...
上岛 遇到极少的抵抗
on the island. Minimal resistance...
火线重案组 第三季 第9集
the.wire.s03e09
* When you walk through the garden *
* you gotta watch your back *
* well I beg your pardon *
* walk the straight and narrow track *
* if you walk with Jesus *
* he's gonna save your soul *
* you gotta keep the devil *
* way down in the hole *
* he's got the fire and the fury *
* at his command *
* well you don't have to worry *
* if you hold on to Jesus hand *
* we'll all be safe from Satan *
* when the thunder rolls *
* just gotta help me keep the devil *
* way down in the hole *
* you gotta help me keep the devil *
当你在等待永远不会到来的时刻 -- Freamon
挖深点 我明白
Deep into it, I see.
嗯 包在我们身上
Yeah, we getting there.
你的看法是对的
You looking correct.
星期天早上 我要去参加弥撒的 知道吗?
Sunday morning. I'm on my way to hear the Word, you know?
你赔钱付给那些人?
You paying those guys out of pocket?
锅炉在运作 管道没问题
Boiler in there's working and the pipes are okay.
我想 明天前得清场
I should have it all cleaned out  by tomorrow, I think.
你们只差许可证了
All you gonna need is the permits.
- 许可证? - 对 许可证
- Permits? - Yeah. Permits.
- 是他? - 妈的
- Yo, was that him? - Shit.
如果不是 不过损失一颗子弹而已
If it ain't, we'd only be wasting a bullet.
最大的问题是现在是礼拜日早上 你懂吗?
Only problem is it being Sunday  morning and all, you know?
- 你打给谁? - Slim Charles 老兄
- Who you calling? - Slim Charles, man.
你跟我说 在集体开会前有什么不爽都摆出来 对吗?
You told me we supposed to bring our beefing before the group, right?
而你呢 在角落和那小伙Marlo开战
Here it is you warring with the young boy, Marlo, over corners.
Marlo不是自己人
Marlo ain't in the group.
虽然这么说 这些垃圾麻烦对生意无益
Be that as it may, all this  shoot-em-up shit is bad for business.
警察在一半的西区街角盯着我们
We got cops on half the West Side corners.
而那些没盯梢的地方  我又不敢派兄弟们去
And what corner they ain't holding, I can't have my people standing on for fear...
担心他们会被当成Barksdale的人 吃子弹
they gonna be mistaken as one of Barksdale people and catch a bullet.
听好 我也试过和那小伙谈谈 但...
Look, man, I tried to talk to  the young buck myself, but...
你得跟Avon谈 因为一半的问题都出在那里
You try talking to Avon. Because that's half the problem right there.
完全同意
No doubt, exactly.
- 对 - 是的
- Yeah. - That's it.
我就这个意思
That's what I'm saying, man.
黑鬼可能还在睡
Nigga probably sleeping in.
是这样的 Stringer 你的人
Fact is, Stringer, your man needs  to reconcile himself...
要接受新思想
to this new way of thinking.
你可以提醒他 就像在这屋里的所有人
Now, you could remind him that,  like everyone else in this room...
他可以从我的门路和批发价中获益
he benefiting from my connect  and from the wholesale price...
- 我们得团结协作才行啊 - 他懂的 别这样 Joe
- we got by throwing in together. - I mean, he know that, come on, Joe.
那现在我们找他帮个忙
Well, so, now we coming to  him for help with a little something.
他应该他妈的收敛一下  别侵犯年轻成员的地盘
He need to just back the fuck off and let the young gun keep his corners.
你自己说的 我们不能在争地盘了
Now, you said yourself it  can't be about territory no more.
- 积习难移 - 谁?
- Old habits die hard. - Who this?
对 是我
Yeah, it's me.
对 我们在那家伙的家
Yeah, we on the house  where the dude is, you know...
- 说重点 黑鬼 - 妈的 我努力不提到名字
- Talk, nigga. - Shit, man, I'm trying not to use names.
听着 是Gerard  我们盯着Omar 他会走出房子的
Look, this Gerard, man. And we're on Omar, he gonna come out the house.
你懂的  我也不想在争地盘上死弟兄
As you know, I ain't trying to lose no niggas on them corners, either...
但是一条大道分两边的啊 你懂吗?
but it's a two-way street, you know?
说吧 伙计
Go ahead, man.
Gerard和Sapper盯着Omar
Gerard and Sapper got their sights on Omar.
试过打给Slim 但打不通
Tried to reach Slim and he ain't answering.
- 所以呢? - 今天是礼拜日 String
- So? - It's church day, String.
星期天早上 知道吗?
Sunday morning, you know?
- 他们确定是他? - Omar 是的
- They sure it's him? - Omar, yeah.
好吧 动手
All right, do it.
动手
Do it.
Gerard 他们在那里 上吧
Gerard. They right there, come on.
好的 你请吧
All right, here you go.
噢 我的天!噢 我的天!
Oh, my goodness! Oh, my goodness!
这一次 我肯定打中他了
This time, I definitely hit him.
整个区的范围 14%
District-wide, it's 14%.
在西区这样的犯罪率下降幅度 从未听说过
A drop like that in the Western  felony rate, that's unheard of.
但天知道当你的秘密被揭露时 会发生什么
But God knows what happens  when you let go of your secret.
嘿 是福不是祸 是祸躲不过
Hey, what happens, happens.
他们是想让我的继续试点下去...
I mean, if they want to keep  my little experiment going...
还是想按常规办事 都听他们的 但我呢?
or they want to go back to business as usual. That's on them. But me?
到时候我已经走了 D 离开了 Hopkins联系我了
I'm out of here, D, I'm gone.  And Hopkins came through.
昨天我收到当保安的工作合约
I got a contract offer on  that security job yesterday.
- 你真的要退休? - 一直都想
- You really gonna retire? - Always planned to.
怎么了?
What?
你不想有始有终吗?
You started something.  You ain't gonna finish it?
- 你什么意思? - 在一个你无能为力的...
- What do you mean? - On a battlefield you can't do much...
战场上 你达成了休战 Bunny
to help anybody with anything. But you managed a truce, Bunny.
让街道犯罪合法化 努力加油啊
And making the game street  legal. takes the heart out of it.
继续干下去 我们能改变那些...
Keep it going, we gonna reach  some of those people...
追求麻醉药和毒品的人 甚至跑腿的人啊
chasing dope and coke,  and maybe even some hoppers, too.
你或许可以
You might at that.
但当你交接给下一任时 会怎么样呢
But what happens when you turn  your district over to the next man?
或有人收到了风声 却没人为之辩护 该怎么办?
Or people get wind of this thing and there's no one to defend it? What then?
- 对比度怎么样啊? - 自然光好一点
- How's the contrast on that? - Good for daylight.
是喔?
Yeah?
星期天哎? 搞什么鬼 Lester?
On a Sunday? What the fuck, Lester?
你不也来了
Could say the same of you.
Elena把孩子带回她娘家了  我还能干什么呢?
Elena's taking the kids to her mother's, what the fuck else am I gonna do?
没生活 没婚姻 没孩子
No life, no marriage, no kids.
没问题
No problem.
这摄像头怎么了?
What's with the video?
要把它放在Striner印刷店对面的窗
Gonna put it up in one of the windows across from Stringer's print shop.
记录他的行踪
Catch him coming and going.
- 嘿 要帮忙么? - 你的脸大家都认得
- Hey, you need help? - You're a known face.
我想我和Prez星期天去搞定 商店关门
I figure me and Prez do it on  a Sunday, shop is closed...
扮成工人的样子
you know, looking like working men.
你知道吗 Lester? 我真的相信整个部门里 再也找不到
You know something, Lester? I do believe there aren't five swinging dicks...
五个像我们这样有种的人了
in this entire department who  can do what we do.
我不是自夸或乱说话 我只是 你想想...
I'm not saying, like, all chest-out and shit. It's just, I mean, you think about it...
这里 大概有 3千个宣誓就职的警察吧 对吗?
there's maybe, what, 3,000 sworn, right?
上百个头儿们 他们都毫无头绪
Hundred or so are bosses,  so there's not a fucking clue there.
再有几百个警督 队长
Few more hundred is  sergeants and lieutenants.
大多想日后当老板 所以他们也百无一用
Most of them wanna be bosses one day, so they're just as fucked.
还有6 700个该死的宅在这里的家伙 知道吗?
Then there's 600 or 700 fucking  housecats, you know?
办公室工作人员 至于巡逻队的?
Deskmen. And the patrol division?
估计他们还能有点能力 但在现在这里这副模样...
There's probably a little bit of talent  there,but the way the city is right now...
有1500个人接报出警 维护街道秩序
that's 1,500 guys chasing  calls and clearing corners.
没人知道他该做什么  完全没有成就感 对么?
I mean, nobody's knowing his post, nobody's building nothing, right?
调查科也一样
And CID's the same.
接报警电话 追求尽快破案 完全无心深究
Catching calls, chasing quick clearances, keeping everything in the shallow end.
还有谁 能有我们办案的这种劲头啊?
I mean, who is there out there, can do what we can do with a case?
真的 有多少人呢?
How many are there really?
郡里的Don Worden  Ed Burns  Gary Childs
Don Worden, Ed Burns, Gary  Childs out in the county...
Woodlawn夫人John O'Neil和Steve Cleary
John O'Neil and Steve  Cleary over at Woodlawn.
他们算得上是 但不多 确实不多
Oh, they bring it in, but there's  not many. There's not many.
我们是这行业的精英 Lester 在这里 我们是最牛的
We're good at this, Lester. In this town, we're as good as it gets.
- 天生的警察 - 妈的 没错 天生的警察
- Natural police. - Fuck, yes, natural police.
告诉我 Jimmy 你觉得结案之后会怎样?
Tell me something, Jimmy. How exactly do you think it all ends?
- 你什么意思? - 接受检阅?金手表?
- What do you mean? - A parade? A golden watch?
一个闪亮亮的属于Jimmy McNulty的日子 等你再带了案子来
A shining Jimmy-McNulty-Day  moment when you bring in a case...
每个人都会聚在一起 说
so sweet everybody gets together and says...
"噢 妈的 他一直都是对的 我们早该听他的"
"Oh, shit, he was right all along. We should've listened to the man."
这工作可救不了你 Jimmy
The job will not save you, Jimmy.
不会让你功成名就  不会让你变得更牛逼
It won't make you whole,  it won't fill your ass up.
- 不知道 一个好案子... - 结束 案子都会结束
- I don't know. A good case... - Ends. They all end.
抓到人 就都结束了
The handcuffs go click and it's over...
第二天早上 你还是会独自从你房间里醒来
and the next morning it's  just you in your room with yourself.
还会有下一个案子啊
Until the next case.
天哪 除了工作 你得有自己的生活
Boy, you need something outside of this here.
比如什么? 玩具屋模型吗?
Like what? Dollhouse miniatures?
嘿嘿嘿 生活 生活 Jimmy 你懂吗?
Hey, hey, hey. A life. A life,  Jimmy, you know what that is?
在你等待永远不会来的时刻的时候 你就得生活
It's the shit that happens while you're waiting for moments that never come.
- 星期天早上动手? - 我们打来问过
- On a Sunday morning? - We called to ask.
Shamrock说可以动手
And Shamrock said to go.
在星期天早上 当一黑鬼带他老祖母去祷告
On a Sunday morning,  y'all try to hit a nigga...
你们向他开枪...
when he taking his  wrinkle-ass grandmas to pray.
你们也没打中那黑鬼
And y'all don't hit the nigga, neither.
你们就打中了祖母的帽子?
All y'all kill is grandma's crown?
在Sham说去之前 Omar就已经在出租车附近了
And by the time Sham say go,  Omar damn near in the cab.
你们的所为违反了礼拜日早上的停战规矩
Ain't enough y'all done  violated the Sunday morning truce.
不行! 我站在这拿着一位真心虔诚的
No! I'm standing here holding  a torn-up church crown...
有色人种的女士的被射烂的帽子
of a bona fide colored lady.
知道什么是带有色人种的女士吗? 肯定不是你妈
Do you know what a colored lady is? Not your moms, for sure.
因为如果他们是...
'Cause if they was that...
你们一定不会这么做
y'all would've known  better than that bullshit.
你们有辱Avon Barksdale的名誉了
Y'all trifling with Avon  Barksdale reputation here.
知道吗?
You know that?
她没事吧?
Is she all right, though?
她脸被玻璃划破 我扑倒她的时候 压到的地方也疼
She got cut on her face from the glass and she sore from where I fell on her.
但起码无大碍
But other than that, though.
你救了她?
You saved her ass, huh?
我差点害死那女人
I damn near got that woman killed, yo.
他们帮她缝伤口时  你们真该在Sinai医院看看我
Y'all should've seen me in Sinai Hospital while they stitching her up...
撒谎解释为什么 大街上有人想杀我的囧样子
lying about why somebody  wanna shoot me down in the street.
那女人我以为我在餐馆里工作
That woman think I work in a cafeteria.
- 餐馆? - 机场 对
- Cafeteria? - At the airport, yeah.
机场? 为什么?
The airport? Why the airport?
因为她永远不会去那里吃饭啊
'Cause I know she ain't never gonna go down there to go dining, that's why.
嘿 Kimmy 这不好笑 是她养大了我!
Hey, yo, Kimmy, this ain't funny,  yo. That woman raised me!
只要我活着一天 每个月我都带她去一次做礼拜
And, for as long as I been grown, once a month I been with her on a church Sunday.
告诉自己没必要担心  因为这城市没有人
Telling myself ain't no need to  worry 'cause there ain't nobody...
会下作到在星期天早上行恶
in this city that low-down to  disrespect a Sunday morning.
你们知道我准备收手了 对吧? 你们知道吧?
Y'all know I was gonna walk away, right? Y'all know that, right?
我是说 Tosha之后 我就打算不管那些事儿了
I mean, after Tosha, I was gonna  leave them people be, yo.
- Avon现在回来了 - 噢 Barksdale必须搞掉
- Avon home now. - Oh, Barksdale got to go.
Stringer也还是 这事得结束 兄弟!
Stringer, too. This thing got to end, man!
我对天发誓 星期天早上 他们打掉了她最好看的帽子
I swear to God, yo, on a Sunday morning, they near shot her best crown off, yo.
这群无羞耻心的黑鬼! 兄弟 你们懂我吧?
I mean, no shame, them niggas! Man, y'all feel me?
我要退出
I'm out.
如果你回去对付Barksdale的人 我就退出
If you back to dealing with  Barksdale people, I'm out, yo.
我加入是为了挣钱
I'm in it for the money.
在别的地方挣更容易
It's easier out there than that.
那就剩你和我了 像从前那样
Just you and me then. Like it was.
不行 这是我自己的事情
No, yo. This one about me.
- 与别人无关 - 嘿 我挺你的
- And nobody else. - Hey, I'm with you.
这件事不行 你不可以
Not on this one, you ain't.
好吧 伙计们
Okay, guys.
我们还差一点 就可以监听他们了
We are maybe a step and a half away from being up on a wire on these people.
我们所需的是抓紧做出调查...
All we need is to firm up the PC...
说明这些一次性手机是在贩毒中使用的
showing the disposable phones are being used in a drug conspiracy.
McNulty和Greggs 你们负责
McNulty and Greggs, you're on that angle.
你们要么当卧底 要么给线人戴上监听器材
You need to walk either  an undercover or a wired CI...
接近Barksdale的手下
up to one of the Barksdale crews.
Lester 你和Prez写起诉书
Lester, you and Prez start  typing affidavits...
因为如果我们拿到证据
because when the probable cause comes in...
我们要第一时间拿到申请书
we're gonna want to  get the application in fast.
警探 你负责追查Bernard
Detective, you're the chaser  on our boy Bernard.
当他出来买电话 我们就跟着他
When he goes out for cell  phones, we're right behind.
我们越快得到新的号码
The faster we get ahold of the new numbers...
我们越快能监听到电话
the faster we're up on those phones.
现在 当Caroline休假回来
Now, when Caroline comes back off vacation...
她会负责监视迷你摄像机
she's gonna be on the mini-cam.
从现在起我们记录下Stringer的一举一动
From here on out we keep a  log on any movement by Stringer...
同时盯着Barksdale先生
and we keep an eye out for  Mr. Barksdale as well.
试着整理出他的日程表
Try to get a line on where  he spends his days.
至于我 我得赶去和无线电公司做个斗争
As for me, I'm off to do battle  with the wireless company.
他们那边有问题?
They a problem?
自从这烂东西被发明 就存在了
Have been since the damn  things were invented.
好吧
Okay, then.
记住为了这次监听 我们现在要和时间赛跑
Remember that with this wire,  everything is a race against the clock.
现在我们得到的线索都是暂时的
Anything we get up on is only temporary.
- 你联系到Bubbles了? - 对 他会在Mount Clare等
- You reach Bubbles? - Yeah. He'll be waiting at Mount Clare.
- Lee DNR日志在哪? - 啥?
- Lee, where's the DNR log? - What?
日志
The log.
没关系 找到了
Never mind, I got it right here.
全部都是Stringer 时时刻刻监视
All Stringer, all the time.
请找Theresa D'Agostino
Theresa D'Agostino, please.
- 能等等吗? - 对 我等着
- Can you hold, please? - Yeah, I'll hold.
抱歉 她现在不在办公室 要留口信吗?
I'm sorry, she's not in the office now. You wanna leave a message?
不 我已经留了一个了
No, I left one already.
- 拳击健身房? - 给孩子们用的 运动俱乐部
- A boxing gym? - For kids and all. An athletic club.
"健身房 减肥沙龙  公共浴室只能在B2 B3"
"Gyms, reducing salons, public baths are permitted only in properties zoned...
" B4或者B5的范围内出现"
"B2, B3, B4 or B5."
要由注册建筑师  工程师签名和封存
All signed and sealed by a  registered architect and engineer...
楼板骨架规划 包括工作量标准
Floor framing plan,  including the load criteria...
液体循环加热管道 设备布局
Hydronic piping and equipment layouts.
六份消防措施计划
Six copies of your fire protection plan...
还有紧急出口 自动喷淋装置
with emergency exits and  sprinkler system noted.
还有卫生部门的批准 因为你这是个体育与文化健康服务机构
Health Department since it's a  physical culture and health service.
还要有由Calvert街的国家体育委员会 发放的许可证
A license from the State Athletic  Commission up on Calvert Street.
- 中型还是大型? - 中型
- Mid-size or full? - Mid-size.
你应该升级 买辆凯迪拉克
You should upgrade and get  one of them Escalades.
有XM无线电之类的
They got that XM radio and all.
我的意思是 如果我们整天都要待在这破车里 值得买 Bernard
I'm saying if we gonna be in that damn car all damn day, it's worth it, Bernard.
- 你怕痒 Bubs? - 有点冷 Kima
- You ticklish, Bubs? - The chills, Kima.
你帮我弄吧
You do that to me.
这是交易用的钱 Bubs  记得过程会被录下来的
Here's the buy money, Bubs.  Remember, this is all on tape.
知道了
I hear you.
在Vincent街 他们甚至都不掖着藏着了
So, down there on Vincent Street, they don't even hide the ground stash anymore.
观察 等待时机 看看他们什么时候放松戒备
You watch and wait, see when  they're running low...
要大约30片 让他们打电话补货
and ask for 30 or so. Enough so that they have to call for a quick re-up.
这很重要 要让他用手机
That's the important thing.  We want him to use his burner.
- 好的 那30片就留给我了哈  - 吃掉你就没命了 Bubs
All right. I get to keep the 30. Thirty'd kill you, Bubs.
你可以留住我们给你的钱
You get to keep the money we hand you...
不过你拿到货 就得回来这里
once you come back here  with all of that product.
- 我只是随口问问 - 我只是提醒你
- I was just asking. - Just telling.
- 不可能 - 什么?
- It can't be done. - Excuse me?
你想要激活信息?
The activation information you're gonna want?
除非开始计费 否则营业厅也获取不到的
That stuff's not accessible from the business office until it goes to billing...
那至少要等几天 甚至1个星期以上
and that takes a few days,  sometimes a week or more.
不过更重要的是  我们每月都有一堆法庭申请
But, more than that, we have dozens of law enforcement inquiries every month.
我们按接收顺序准备资料 现在的周期是30天
We get to them in the order received and currently the turnaround's 30 days.
30天?
Thirty days?
让我理清一下头绪
Let me understand something.
你公司正在做一次性手机的生意
Your company is in business selling  disposable cell phones...
而且顾客在购买手机时
to people who don't have to  give any subscriber information...
- 无需提供任何身份资料 对吗? - 对
- at the time of purchase, correct? - Correct.
你们认为 他们买了手机
They buy these phones and  as far as you're concerned...
匿名使用 预先付话费
they use them anonymously,  pre-paying for their minutes...
从零售商那买 对
From the retailers, yes.
当他们匿名使用手机 无论出于什么原因
And while they're using these phones anonymously, for whatever purpose...
他们都无法被法律监督 就因为贵公司
they can't be monitored by law  enforcement because your company...
无法在一个月内 对法院要求窃听的命令做出反应?
can't react within a month to  a court order for a wiretap?
- 我们尽力了 - 狗屁
- We do the best we can. - This is bullshit.
你在卖手机 帮助毒贩交易
You're selling a phone that you know  is effective for drug trafficking.
队长 我们的预付费服务是为了年轻人
Lieutenant, our prepaid inventory  is there for young people...
大学生之类的 买不起手机的人群
college students and such, people who can't afford a permanent cell phone plan.
哪个大学生买不起手机?
What college student can't  afford a cell phone?
他们负担得起读大学的钱 就能买得起手机
They can afford the fucking college, they can afford the phone that goes with it.
你非常不同意你的意见
I resent the suggestion.
那我阐明一下 你在告诉我 纵使我们能
Just so I'm clear, you're telling me that even if by some miracle we are able...
在毒贩使用贵公司产品时 逮捕他
to get up on a drug dealer's disposable cell phone in time to catch him talking...
你还是得用1个月激活窃听
you're gonna take as much as  a month to activate our tap.
如果你觉得不妥 可以联系我们的总法律顾问
Well, if you have a problem with that, your office can contact our general counsel.
我话说到此
That's all I can say.
不如这样?巴尔的摩的州律师
How about this? How about the State's  Attorney for Baltimore City...
在法院大楼开记者会 宣布
calls a press conference on the  courthouse steps to declare that...
Bay无线电公司协助市里最强悍的毒贩
Bay Wireless is in league with the most violent drug traffickers in the city...
为他们排忧解难 逃避法律制裁
preventing their apprehension  and arrest by law enforcement.
4到5天处理时间 我们只能做到这样
Four to five days turnaround. Best we can do.
我发誓 我感觉像个泄气的气球
I swear, I felt like a damn balloon  with air rushing out my ass...
四处漂
going from desk to desk.
这是新成员啊?
This is our new man, huh?
- Frank Reid - Dennis Wise
- Frank Reid. - Dennis Wise.
牧师 Dennis花了一天在Benton大厦
Reverend, our man Dennis spent all day...
争取许可证
down at the Benton Building,  trying for permits.
- 新健身房的许可证? - 对
- On the new gym? - Yeah.
你提我的名字没?
You use my name?
你提了谁的名字了么
You use anybody's name?
伙计 我其实是有机会提Smith和Wesson的
Hell, man. There was a time I'd  have used Smith and Wesson.
不 伙计 我是说 你们普通人是怎么办到的?
No, look, man, I'm just saying, how y'all regular folk get it done in this town?
Doreen 打给Delegate Watkins 麻烦你
Doreen, ring Delegate Watkins, please.
- 黄色上衣 黄色上衣 - 谢谢 老兄 谢谢
- Yellow tops, yellow tops. - Obliged, man, obliged.
合上它 懂吗? 你告诉你朋友 行吗?
Keeping it close, you know? You tell a friend, okay?
穿黑T恤太热了 对吗?
Too hot for them black tees, right?
- 你好么 小子 你在叫卖什么? - 装尸袋
- What's up, papa, what you hawking? - Body bags.
好吧 我要30片
All right, let me get 30. Thirty pills.
30? 你这烂货
Thirty? Where the fuck your raggedy-ass...
从哪弄来300元买啊?
come up with $300 in motherfucking cash, man?
我卖T恤好几个星期了 知道吧
Well, I've been selling these  T-shirts for weeks now, you know.
我或许穿得很破烂 但我有挣到钱
I mean, I might be raggedy,  but I'm in a cash business.
要挣我的钱不?
You want my money or no?
我们没货了 好吧
Yeah, we out. All right.
很快就到
Shouldn't be long.
买这么多 打个折吧?
A bulk purchase justify a discount, right?
- 250? - 275
- $250 or so? - $275.
- 有几个是白的 - 行啊
- And a couple of them whiteys. - Yeah, that'll work.
- 行啊 - Bubs又挣了25
- That'll work. - Bubs just made another $25.
- 我找Theresa D'Agostino - 抱歉 她不在
- Theresa D'Agostino, please. - I'm sorry, but she's not in.
- 能留口信吗? - 不用了 我再打来
- Can I take a message? - No, I'll call back.
- 怎么样啊? - 啥啊?
- So, how's that working? - What?
- 你新女友 - 到现在为止 一直都还不错
- Your new ho. - So far, so good.
- 你拿收据了吗? - 嗯 大部分吧
- You got the receipts, man? - Yeah, most of them.
一些在州际路那里被吹走了
A few blew out the  damn window on the interstate.
怎么 你们等着看Avon?
What, y'all waiting to see Avon?
听说你们昨天打掉一老太太的帽子
Man, I hear y'all shot the crown  off an old lady's head yesterday.
太好了 你们都来了
Good, y'all made it.
我们干点正事儿吧 上楼谈
Yeah, we putting in some work. Come on upstairs so we can talk.
知道数量了
Back with numbers.
- 多少? - 24部
- How many? - Twenty-four Trac phones.
Catonsville和Sykesville的Mondo超市各两部 4部来自Frederick
Two each from Mondo Marts in Catonsville and Sykesville and four from Frederick...
8部来自West Virginia河边得两站各8部
and then eight each from two  stops over the river in West Virginia.
那些保险杠仪器 很好用
Those bumper beepers? They work great, man.
- 他这次走的是L-70公路了 - 能怪他吗? 风景更美了
- He went out L-70 this time. - Can you blame him? The scenery's better.
24?
Twenty-four, huh?
我们得用拨号录制系统 足够幸运的话
We're gonna have a lot of DNRs up. But with any luck...
其中一个能搭上Bodie Broadus先生
one of these phones leads to young  Mr. Bodie Broadus.
- 你要打给Pearlman? - 没错
- You wanna call Pearlman? - All right.
谁饿了?
Who's hungry?
- 不如吃中国餐? - 好主意
- How about Chinese? - Sounds good to me.
- 你们点餐 我去买 - 我想吃捞面
- You guys call it in and I'll go. - Let me have some of that lo mein.
帮我打这些麻烦资料 我和他去
You take a turn typing this  shit and I'll go with him.
- 我要糖醋的 - 我要捞面
- Make mine sweet and sour. - Lo mein for me.
出发?
Get rolling?
你们和Charles联系 他会告诉你们细节
So y'all get with Charles, he gonna  give you all the details on it.
- 谁啊? - 东区黑鬼
- Who that? - East Side niggas.
想加入我们 Milton帮我们联系上的
Be willing to soldier up for us on retainer. Milton put me up on them.
我们得回去 String 我能感觉到
Man, we gonna be back where we was, String. You know, I can smell it.
我们去找Marlo 然后散伙儿干
We just got to get this boy Marlo and  then we spread out like we do.
他们是一伙的 对这情况不会满意的
Them co-op boys, man, they ain't too happy about this situation, man.
对 他们说被警察盯着 别无选择
Yeah. They say they got cops on corners where they wouldn't have otherwise.
- 大家都时刻戒备 - 去他妈的黑鬼
- Everybody nervous. - Man, fuck them niggas.
Prop Joe说他会去调解 懂我意思吧?
I mean, Prop Joe said he'd mediate.  You know what I mean?
去找Marlo 和他谈谈
Go to Marlo, talk on it.
对 如果他带枪 或许能谈成
Yeah, well, if he take a gun  with him, maybe it could work.
那我问你
Let me ask you something, though.
你有告诉那群黑鬼  他们能从伤到Omar祖母这件事全身而退吗?
Did you tell them discount-ass niggas that they could pop off at Omar grandma?
噢 Sham在会议中间找我
Oh, man. Sham come to me in  the middle of the meeting...
说他们盯着Omar
and talk about they got their sights on Omar.
没交代祖母在场 没提到帽子 什么都没有
They say nothing about no grandma. No church hat, nothing like that.
我听到那混球的名字 就叫他们上
I hear the cocksucker's name, I say, "go."
- 在星期天早上? - 我没想那么多
- On a Sunday morning? - Yo, I don't give a fuck, man.
我只听到混球的名字 没想到是礼拜日
I hear that cocksucker's name, man, I ain't thinking about a church day.
星期天停战协议已经被淡忘了
The Sunday truce been around long  as the game itself, man.
你懂我意思 你可以杀人
I mean, you know what I'm saying,  you can do some shit...
管他妈的 但别在星期天闹事了
and be like "what the fuck," but, hey, just never on no Sunday, man.
大家都在议论我们
I mean, it's just like people  was talking on us and all...
越说越离谱
and the stories are getting  bigger and bigger.
我发誓胖脸Rick听到有人说
Like, I swear to God, Fatface Rick heard that our people went and shot...
我们的人开枪故意打到Omar祖母屁股什么的
Omar granny in the ass on purpose,  and all that.
还说他们拿出了自己的鸡巴 对着那帽子撒尿之类的屁话
And that pulled their dicks out,  pissed on her crown and shit.
不 我也听到同样的话
No, I mean, I heard the same bullshit.
Prop Joe全说了 不过 我能说什么呢?
Prop Joe gave me an earful.  But, yo, what can I say, man?
人手不好找啊
Good help is hard to find.
如果不是这档子事儿 你觉得我会他妈的找东区那些黑鬼办事儿吗?
If it wasn't, you think I'd be paying East Side niggas for shit?
明白 街角我们还是拱手给他们?
Yeah. Yo, we still off them corners?
是的 没办法
Yeah, got to be.
除非我们搞定Marlo 否则回不去
We gonna be off them corners  till we take care of Marlo.
没错 或许我们得找多点人
Yeah, maybe we should  put a couple more crews...
到条子没盯着的地方
on them free zones them cops got.
你懂我吗? 在可以的地方赚钱
You know what I mean?  Take the profit where we can.
- 你觉得可以? - 暂时觉得吧
- You trust that shit? - I mean, so far.
如果他们玩花样 老兄 他们才不会
And if they running game,  man, they ain't gonna get...
只找个小队长来当领头人 对不?
nobody higher than a crew  chief to take a charge, right?
楼下的两个黑鬼 你打算怎么处置?
What you gonna do with them two niggas you got waiting downstairs?
叫他们赔帽子给人家
I gonna make them buy the lady a new hat.
我们在等什么?糖醋?
What're we waiting for? Sweet and sour?
你先吃了许愿饼?
You do the cookie first?
不行吗?
What's the difference?
"新朋友会自己出现在你面前"
"A new friend makes himself known."
他自己?
Himself?
如果是"她自己" 你得是有钱人
If it was "herself,"  then you'd have a fortune.
我娶花园的家具就好了
Shit, I'm married with lawn furniture, man.
技术失控了 肯定是
The technology's out of control, no question.
但是这也不新鲜啊
But that's nothing new.
如今他们用一次性手机
The way these guys are using  disposables nowadays...
我们无法及时监听
we cannot get a working wire up in time.
我们取得用户信息和搞定文书之前
By the time we get subscriber  information and papers served...
他们已经把手机扔了
They're dumping phones.
蜂窝式无线通讯运营商说要1周来搞定文书
Cellular carriers tell them they need nearly a week to process the paperwork.
他们不怎么害怕我们 但如果是FBI呢?
They're only half-scared of us,  but a visit from the Feds?
- 你们有足够资格催促他们 - 不一定
- You all have profile enough to push them. - I don't know.
如果你让他们5天内搞定  我们也只能做到这样
If you've got them down to five days, you're doing about as well as we can.
再说一次 二位 局里最近忙于反恐
Once again, guys, the Bureau's a little  busy with counter-terrorism.
我们的国家律师
And our US Attorney here...
只对政治腐败方面的案子感兴趣
he only touches himself at the  mention of political corruption.
贫民区毒品案子不够格儿啊 我很遗憾
Ghetto drug stuff just doesn't rate.  I'm sorry to say.
这玩意在车里最香了 回家了
Shit always smells best in the car,  going home.
13小队 巷子东边最里面 North Montford 800号
Unit 13. In the alley in the rear,  East Side, 800 North Montford.
- 只有五个街区 我们去 - 走
- That's five blocks, up and over. - Go.
哪个交叉马路? 哪个交叉马路?
What's the cross street? What's the cross street?
交火了
shots fired.
听来像是西Milton
sounded like it was west of milton.
我是警察!他死了 通知总部
i'm police! he's 10-7, call it in.
格洛克手枪
a glock.
他转身时看到枪
i saw the gun as he turned.
是Derrick 上帝啊
it's derrick. jesus christ.
你杀了Derrick 是Waggoner
you killed derrick. it's waggoner.
你妈的杀了Waggoner!
you fucking killed waggoner!
- Greggs - Prez杀了另一警察
- greggs. - prez shot another cop.
- 什么? - 发生在巷子里的意外 前不久的事
- what? - it was an accident in an alley, a little while ago.
- 不是吧 - 我会回你电话的
- no. - i'll call you back.
你为Barksdale而来?
you here for barksdale?
我是为和平而来 伙计  有些莫名其妙的状况发生了
i'm here for peace, man. there's some senseless shit going on.
但Barksdale没派你来?
but barksdale ain't sent you?
不 Stringer知道我在这儿 伙计
no, stringer knows i'm here, man.
如果我能给他们点甜头 他们很可能会投桃报李
if i can bring something respectful back, they most likely to show the same.
告诉那男孩和他同伴可以过来合作
tell the boy he can come in with the co-op.
如果他拿了我们的货 顺便说一句
if he takes our package, which by the way...
比他现在卖的都要好
is better than the best he putting out there now...
他能保住地盘 我保证
he'll keep his corners. guaranteed.
他可能会听 那男孩有想法
he might listen. but the boy got ideas.
他认为现在Avon很弱
and he's thinking avon weak right now.
你见过Avon Barksdale为过什么事情退缩吗?
you ever know avon barksdale to back down from anything?
暗巷中的便衣警察
a plainclothesman in a dark alley,
拔枪后开枪
with his gun out and shots fired.
听着 没人想伤害任何人...
look, no one wants to burn anybody...
但事实是 要考虑到种族因素
but the fact is there's a racial component to consider.
- 看表面... - 他见律师没?
- the appearance of it... - has he seen a lawyer?
队长
lieutenant.
干嘛?
what?
他的处境这样 你无法逼他说
he's in a situation where you can't compel a statement...
除非你宣读出他的权利 但我们还没这么做  所以...
out of him until you read him his rights, and we haven't done that yet, so...
我是他的指挥官 只想知道他是否安好
i'm his commanding officer. i just want to know if he's all right.
好了 不过...
okay, okay, there's just...
此时 这是法律问题了
it's a legal question at this point.
我能为你做什么吗?
can i get you anything?
你该联系工会 Roland
you should call the union, roland.
在你开口之前先和律师聊聊
talk to a lawyer before you say anything further.
我不是说有人要控告你犯罪
i'm not saying anyone's gonna charge anything criminally.
大家都知道你不是故意的...
everyone knows you had no intention of...
但行政上...
but administratively...
你得小心点 因为有种族的问题在
you need to be careful because of the racial thing.
明白吗?
you see that, right?
这部门里会有人这么想的
there's gonna be people in the department who see this that way.
明白吗?
you see that, right?
我没有害怕 没有生气
i wasn't scared, i wasn't angry.
我不管他是黑人还是什么
i didn't give a shit he was black or whatever...
也许我确实有
or maybe i did.
怎么知道你脑子里他妈的有没有啊?
how the fuck do you know if that's in your head or if it's not?
但你看见枪了
but you saw the gun.
对
yeah.
没错 他转向我 然后
yeah, he turned toward me and...
因为你大喊 是吗? 你大喊"警察"  然后他转身?
'cause you shouted, right? you shouted, "police" and he turned, right?
不 不是的 我好像没说什么
no, i don't think so. i don't think i said anything.
我觉得他也没说什么
i don't think he did.
我离巷子就几步远
i was a couple steps in the alley
之后他转身 我看见枪了 就这样
and he turned and i saw the gun. that's all.
他有孩子吗?
did he have kids?
老婆呢?
a wife?
不知道
i don't know.
他们不肯说 他们不会跟我说他
they won't say. they won't talk to me about him.
打给警察协会 找律师 Roland
call the fop. get a lawyer, roland.
不必了 长官 我完了
no, sir. i'm done.
让律师替你说话
let the lawyer talk for you.
队长...
lieutenant...
告诉Lester 我很抱歉
tell lester i'm sorry.
打给工会 他想要律师
call the union. he wants a lawyer in there with him.
等他搞定了之后 你得派人陪他回家
whenever he's done here, you need to send someone home with him.
至少今晚 防止他自杀
for tonight at least, he's a suicide watch.
队长 你会挺他吗?
lieutenant. you'll back him?
我的意思是 如果事情
what i mean is, if this thing should turn...
牵涉到种族问题 你是他的指挥官
into some kind of a black-white thing, you're his unit commander...
他能指望你 对吗?
he can count on you, right?
你没事吧?
you all right?
捞面
lo mein.
真是一团糟
what a clusterfuck.
你和Waggoner认识多久?
how many years on for waggoner?
六年半
six and a half.
2次获表扬 在现任警督成绩里排16
two commendations, 16th on the current sergeants list.
比里面那垃圾好多了
pretty much the exact opposite of that goof in there.
知道那家伙之前的事儿吗
you know what's in that guy's jacket?
他慌了神 开枪打了自己的无线电车
motherfucker flaked out, shot up his own radio car.
他们准备控告他做假报告 然后Valchek介入了
they were gonna charge him with false report until valchek weighed in.
你知道他和Valchek的女儿结婚了吧?
you know he married valchek's daughter, right?
这垃圾还真是有九条命耶
fucking goof had nine lives behind that shit.
八个了
eight up,
当蜂窝式无线通讯公司接到我们传票时
and the rest still to be activated...
其它的还在激活中
whenever the cellular company gets to our subpoenas.
你做得很好了 警探
you did good, detective.
那我们现在找什么?
so we're looking for what?
找有关于Bodie线索的那部电话
looking for one of these phones to give us a signature on our man bodie.
看看有没有打给他女友 他祖母的电话
calls to his girlfriend, his grandmother.
监控所有从一次性手机里拨出的号码
the numbers we pulled off the burners.
看到那些号码 就知道是他的电话了
we see that, we know it's his phone.
如果知道是他的电话  那就肯定是用来贩毒的电话
we know it's his phone, we know he use it to sell drugs.
我们就都知道了
we know all that.
然后我们就要监听  然后祈祷他不会马上扔掉手机
then we get a tap up and pray like hell he doesn't throw it away anytime soon.
Prez乐意见此情景
prez would love this.
我没有对你们撒谎
i ain't gonna lie to you all.
除了拳击那部分 我什么都不知道
i don't know about nothing except the boxing part.
就这样
that's all i was thinking.
你是拳师?
were you a pug?
曾经是 但后来荒废了
yeah, i was. but i got sidetracked, though.
在Reverend Reid看来
well, reverend reid seems to think you'd be quite a draw...
能给你个机会帮助我们这的小混混
for some of these corner kids that we got.
市区里的帮不了吗?
they didn't think so downtown?
其实呢
well, the fact is
你得在第四区找个地方开健身房了
you're looking to put your gym in the fourth district.
那市政会成员就会变Eunetta Perkins了
so your councilperson would be eunetta perkins.
知道她是谁吧?
do you know miss perkins?
很少人知道 很少啊
well, few of us do anymore. few of us do.
由于我们不能完全依赖Perkins小姐
well, since we can't really rely on miss perkins...
Daniels小姐会跟你去
miss daniels here will go with you.
她到这 是由于市政会成员要为选民服务
she's here because constituent service is the life of a city councilperson.
她得亲力亲为
she needs to get a taste of that.
至少我是这么想的
at least i hope i do.
我多口问多一句 Watkins先生  你为什么要帮我?
if you don't mind me asking, mr. watkins. why are you doing this?
你认识Reverend Reid是谁吗?
do you know who reverend reid is?
我选区的选民都知道
well, the voters in my district do.
今天来的?
this came today?
现在看来 一团糟啊
well, now, see, this is fucked up.
我给你二百五十万 就是让他们告诉我 我的报告
oh, i give you $250,000 to have them tell me my paperwork...
不够授权我成为开发商的吗 不是吗?
is insufficient enough to certify me as a developer in the empowerment zone?
对啊 对 你可以说是一团糟
yeah, yeah, you could call it fucked up.
听着 我知道我们找到了对的人
look, i know we touched the right people.
就让我来搞定他们 把问题解决
just let me get with them, clear this mess right up.
搞定他们
get with them.
嘿 交给我 String
hey, i'm on it, string.
你拿到了电灯泡专营权了没?
you got the light bulb franchise, right?
获批准了 现在
that came through. now...
有三万块收回来 但你拿了二十五万啊
you talking about $30,000 coming back. i'm talking about the $250,000 that you took.
你得打给Goose先生 那水龙头先生...
now, you need to call mr. goose, mr. faucet...
你必须得打给他们 因为你收了我的钱 懂吗?
whoever the fuck you gotta call because i gave you money to run, remember that?
这跟贩毒交易不同的 String
it ain't like no drug deal, string.
妈的 钱没有脚
hell, man, you don't put your money...
不会自己找上门的
on the street and have it come right back. it don't work like that.
噢 不会吗?
oh, it don't, huh?
耐心点 兄弟
patience, my man.
政府官僚通常都是自成一派
sometimes with the bureaucracy...
自扫门前雪
the one hand don't know what the other is all about.
你知道我是怎么看的吗? 我看到一只手在我的口袋里
yeah, well, you know what i see? i see one hand in my pocket...
另一只扯着你的鸡巴
while the other hand seem to have grabbed your dick.
该死的Prez
fucking prez.
感觉这很不靠谱啊
i don't even feel like working.
- Sanny 宝贝 - 欢迎来到西区 二位
- sanny, baby. - welcome to the western, guys.
Pryzbylewski的事?
that thing with pryzbylewski?
上帝啊
jesus christ.
真他妈的遗憾 伙计
so fucking sad, man.
你在巡逻吗?
so you humping a wagon, huh?
妈的 对
fuck, yes.
感觉如何啊?
how's that working out for you?
Jimmy 我就爱这个工作
jimmy, i love this fucking gig.
Rawls对我做过最好的事情 就是把我扔回来巡逻
the best thing rawls ever did for me was to knock me back to a district.
没压力 没斗争 8小时工作制
no stress, no struggle. i work eight-hour shifts.
回家毫无负担
i take nothing home with me.
不 我说真的 现在很开心
no, really, i couldn't be happier.
查了这么多年棘手的凶杀案 为了什么啊?
all those years knocking my head against a wall on homicide and for what?
养老金还不够我养伤呢
the same fucking pension with twice the heartburn.
我很高兴你脱困了 Mike
well, i'm glad you landed on your feet, mike.
- 喂 - 你打去办公室找我?
- hello. - you called my office?
对啊 几次
yeah, i did, several times.
真的吗 干嘛?
really, why?
你觉得呢?
why do you think?
过来睡 你想先吃晚餐?
a sleepover. you wanna get dinner first?
不如今晚吧?
how about tonight?
第15街附近的Georgia Brown吧?
georgia brown's down near 15th street.
可以 要我订位吗?
that'll work. you want me to make a reservation?
不 我无需订位
no, i can always get a table there.
好吧 无所谓
all right, whatever.
约在7点半吧
let's shoot for 7.:30.
到时见
i'll see you then.
- 再见 - 再见
- bye. - bye.
联系上了?
you in?
你觉得怎么样?
what do you think?
颜色好看
nice colors.
有讲台吗?
you got a platform?
在学校办 当然有
schools.
觉得自己该是个爱教育的市长呢
thought i'd be the education mayor.
祝你好运 Tony
well, good luck, tony.
我认真的
i mean it.
谢了 兄弟
thanks, man.
- 你什么时候公布?  - 我想在下个月
when do you announce? next month, i think.
尽快离开 开始筹集资金
you know, get out there early, start raising money.
事实上 我觉得在这之前 我就能找到投资方 知道不?
in fact, i thought i'd make the rounds of some people... before then, you know?
探探底
feel them out.
- 什么 Watkins吗? - 嘿 他看来挺喜欢我
what, watkins? hey, he seems to like me.
什么 你真的觉得Odell Watkins 会背叛市长那阵营吗?
what, you really think odell watkins is gonna split from the mayor's camp?
你所能做的是  找一两个话题谈谈口风
what you could do is, you know, feel him out on an issue or two.
这样的话 情况就微妙了  你得先吸引到那家伙
you go in that way, it's more subtle. you know, you gotta charm the guy first.
然后跟他谈谈 然后察言观色
talk to him about the issues and then down the road...
探他口风 看他是否认同你
see if he's willing to throw sunshine on your ass.
同意
i like that.
我们就怎么办吧
we should do that.
我们?
we?
我以为你会跟我一起
i was thinking maybe you would ticket your white ass up with me.
竞选议会主席
make a run for council president.
我呢 胜算最大 新兴的黑人领导
me at the top of the ticket... an emerging black leader,
帅气 雄辩
handsome, well-spoken.
你呢 白人的希望 市民改革之声
you, the great white hope, the new voice of civic reform.
我们可以跟Royce赛一赛
we could give royce a run, man.
为什么你会认为我对议会主席有兴趣?
and what makes you think i'm interested in council president?
不然你他妈的想干嘛?
what the hell else you got going?
考虑一下
think about it.
看看他 像开了灯见到蟑螂
look at them. like roaches when you turn the lights on.
什么意思?
what's it look like?
头和躯干各中一枪 这有两个弹壳
head and torso. you got two casings over here.
先别通知总部
hold the call.
大家都在支持无暴力区域Hampsterdam的说法 哈?
so much for the no-violence-in-hampsterdam theory, huh?
Herc...
herc...
帮忙搬尸体
help them move the body.
- 什么? - 搬出这个街区 离开自由区
- what? - just up the block, just out of the free zone.
Carv 你脑子秀逗了?
carv, you lost your fucking mind?
在救护车来宣布他死亡之前  我们能搞定的
before the ambo gets here to pronounce him, we can do it.
为什么?
why?
如果重案组来了 他们会调查
because if homicide gets here... if they do any kind of canvass...
他们会把这里的情况传开
they're gonna get wind of this shit on the sixth floor downtown.
很好啊
good.
Herc 来嘛
herc, come on.
不行 伙计 不行
no way, man. no way.
去你妈的条条框框 去他妈的
fuck those stripes. fuck them.
嘿 Toke Gil 帮我搬他出Hamsterdam区
hey, toke, gil, help me move this guy out of hamsterdam.
我会是第一个到场的警官 责任我担
i'll be first officer at the scene. it's my responsibility.
别忘了弹壳
don't forget the casings.
记得打给我
make sure that you call me.
- 我会的 谢谢 - 一定要告诉我 好吗?
- i will. thank you. - let me know, okay?
- 保重  - 好的
take care. all right.
好耶!
yes!
7-60呼叫KGA
7-60 to kga.
请讲 7-60
go ahead, 7-60.
700 10-11 我位置在Vincent街 在Fayette后面
have 700, 10-11 me on vincent street, below fayette.
收到 Vincent街 在Fayette南边
10-4, vincent south of fayette.
嘿 你说你和这家伙一起工作?
hey. you say you worked with this guy?
三枪 不说话就开枪 他怕黑人还是怎么?
three shots, no warnings. he scared of black people or something?
妈的
shit.
这事儿太离谱了
the shit's gone too far, man.
嘿 还要你说
hey, you're telling me.
告诉我报社电话号码 太阳报
yeah, i need the number to the newspaper, the sun.
记者电话 新闻部的 对
yeah, the number for the reporters. the newsroom, yeah.
你无话可说吗?
so, you ain't gonna say nothing on it?
有什么好说的呢?
what is there to say?
- Avon 我们家的血肉啊 家人 - 我知道
- avon, this is blood. family. - i know it.
我说的是 可能是有人故意要搞我们  Avon 搞我们家
and i'm telling you that someone may have one this to us, avon. to our family.
警察只会说废话
the cop's just saying that shit.
扰乱你思维
to mess with your head.
- 就是 - 为什么?
- exactly. - why?
警察根本不认识我 我对他来说算什么?
that cop don't know me for shit. what the hell am i to him?
他知道你会认为
he know you're gonna wanna think this thing...
他不会做出这种事
that d, you know, he wouldn't do what he did.
我的确这么认为!
i do think it!
是不是他惹了什么人? 牢里的人?
was it some beef he had? someone on the inside?
警察说这是有人故意造成的假象
that cop said it was someone who didn't want you to know...
让你以为他是自杀
and so they made it look like it did.
没人造假象
nobody did nothing.
- 可警察说... - 他撒谎
- but the cop said... - he's lying.
他职责所在嘛
he paid to lie.
Avon 你是我兄弟
avon, you are my brother.
我必须知道真相
i need to know this more than anything.
他没想出卖我们
he did not roll on us.
他是快招架不住了  但是他还是想通罢手了
he came to the edge, but he turned around and walked away.
我知道他愿意为他的家庭做点什么
and i know he was willing to do what he had to for his family.
为我们坐垫什么
for us.
但我必须知道 你心知肚明
but i need to know that you know that.
确定你也这么看他
that you saw him that way.
什么? 你想说什么?
what? what you trying to say?
如果有事发生了
if something happened...
你他妈的想什么呢?
the fuck are you even thinking?
你觉得这事和我有关? 我会杀我家人?
that i had something to do with it? i could do that to my own kin?
你是怎么想的吗?你他们的这么认为的?
is that what you fucking think? the fuck is in your head?
我没对D做过什么 我和这事一点关系没有
i ain't do nothing to d. i ain't had shit to do with it.
跟什么没有关系?
to do with what?
什么没有关系?
发生的那些事儿啊
whatever happened.
发生的那些事儿啊 Brianna
whatever it is that happened, brianna.
你认为我会不清楚自己的事务吗?
you think i don't know my business?
- 你这么认为吗? - 我懂了 我看得出尸体从那个街区搬过来
- is that what you think? - look i understand. i can see the body was moved from the block.
明早我能把他交给你
i can get him to you tomorrow morning.
让我看看能否找到他
just let me see if i can find him.
我能办妥的
look, i'll make good on this.
搞定它
take care of this.
- 他说什么? - 他们找到血迹 一路找到那街区
- what'd he say? - they found a blood trail going back up the block.
或许...
so maybe...
被弄花了 带有毒品的痕迹
smeared, with drag marks.
他们在另一端找到第三颗弹壳
and they also found a third casing at the other end.
妈的
shit.
那怎么办?
so what's the deal?
能怎么办 明早之前搞定这件事
the deal is, we turn this into a dunker by tomorrow morning...
否则 他会写报告给情报处还有副局那边
or he starts typing a report for isd and the deputy ops.
- 我操 - 不 是我操!
- fuck me. - no, fuck me!
你没有移动尸体 警官
look, you didn't move that body, sergeant.
是我搬的 懂吗?
i moved the body. you understand?
你尊重你都是为了我的安排
look, i respect that you did what you did on behalf...
才这么做 但责任在我
of what i'm trying to do down here, but the responsibility is mine.
那我们怎么办?
well, so what do we do?
基本上 他的意思是 他不打算再投入任何新的资源了
he basically said he wasn't gonna commit any new resources...
尽管他将其放入了
though he has placed it on the agenda...
司法公正协调会的日程上了
of the coordinating council on criminal justice, for what that's worth.
可怜的Clarence 他看起来很累
poor clarence. he's looking tired.
所以我们得求助于州议会大厦
so we're looking for help from the state house.
如果城市能给个几百几千...
if the city could get a couple hundred thousand...
我们可以有资金去支付加班保护这些人员的费用
we could afford an overtime detail to protect these folks.
我明白如果市长支持 会简单很多 但
i know this is an easier sell with the mayor involved, but...
- 你能说服他吗? - Clarence?
- could you convince him? - clarence?
他听不进去的
he barely listens anymore.
上帝 就是啊
jesus, tell me about it.
我当了三年议员 一直都被他妈的忽略
i mean, i been a councilman for three years now... that's a long fucking time to be ignored.
我的意思是规则被打破了
i'm saying the rules got broke.
我的人守住承诺了
my people kept their promises...
怎么说就怎么做 他们说到做到
they did what they said and they were as good as their word.
你们
y'all,
你们违背了承诺
y'all ain't keep up your end of it.
不是我的人
wasn't my people.
现在我才不要分出是谁干的
look, i ain't making those distinctions right now.
事实是 有人带枪到自由区 并开了枪
the fact is, somebody brought a gun up in the free zone and used it.
这些都违背了约定
and both those things against the promises made.
如果这里有死人 我就无法保证这里
now, i can't justify this shit if i got dead bodies up in there.
我的意思是 明天过来
so, what i'm saying is this, come tomorrow...
如果我还没找到凶手的话
if i don't have a shooter in bracelets...
那整个Hamsterdam的事儿就玩完
this whole hamsterdam affair is over,
一切就都结束
it's finished.
我会让我的人都去街角
i'm gonna take my people back up on the corners...
整天搞你吗
and we gonna fuck y'all every way we can.
听到没?
- you hear me? - ???
这地方存在大家都相安无事的 对吧?
yeah, it was good while it lasted, huh?
你们有钱交易 也不用交保释金
you had cash on the barrel and you ain't never need no bail money.
这样一来  我看到哪个街角 都不会乌烟瘴气的
and hell, i had clean corners everywhere i looked.
但明天 这些都不可能了
but all that gonna be gone tomorrow,
除非你们交出枪手
unless y'all bring me my shooter.
你觉得会成吗?
you think that'll work?
你说呢?
do you?
真好吃
that's good food.
你怎么知道这地方的
how'd you know about this place?
克林顿总统时期 这里很出名
it was big when clinton was in.
这个和丹参
this and the red sage.
现在都是牛排餐厅和雪茄吧了
now it's all steakhouses and cigar bars.
你住在这 但你大部分时间在巴尔的摩 对吗?
so you live here, but you spend a lot of time in baltimore, right?
我在那里上班
i have work up there.
还在山上有点圣玛丽校友会的事儿
and the alumni stuff with st. mary's on the hill.
我在UM法学院上过学 所以在那有关系
i went to um law, so i still have connections there, too.
事实上 我在家乡长大
actually, i grew up in homeland.
是吗?
yeah?
我是在Lauraville
lauraville for me.
你在哪上大学?
where'd you go to college?
Loyola 只读了一年
loyola. only one year.
我女友怀孕了 所以...
my girlfriend got pregnant, so...
怎么呢?
so?
所以...
so...
所以你在巴尔的摩当警察了 干得怎么样啊?
so you became a cop in baltimore. how's that working for you?
很好啊
it's pretty good.
我负责高端毒品案件 窃听
you know. i do a lot of high-end drug stuff. wiretaps.
长时间调查暴力罪犯 之类的
prolonged investigations of violent offenders, that kind of stuff.
事实上 部门里是没有很多
fact is, there's not a lot of guys in the department...
胜任的人的 这些需要有点...
who can do that kind of thing. you know, it takes a certain...
我也不知道 你一定会很喜欢这工作
i don't know, you gotta love it.
追逐的快感之类的
thrill of the chase and all that.
你的工作是怎么样的?
so, you do what in politics?
做政治竞选
i do political campaigns.
竞选经理人吗?
you mean like a campaign manager?
更像是个策划师
more of a strategist really.
不需要每天工作 但策划就是要计划怎么去赢
not so much the day-to-day stuff... but the strategy of how a candidate can win.
类似一个顾问
a consultant of sorts.
你有帮巴尔的摩的什么人做策划吗?
you strategizing for anyone in baltimore?
我不能说
i shouldn't say.
他还没正式公开呢
i mean, he hasn't officially announced anything yet.
他人好吗?
All right. he any good?
嘿 你为他工作 我就投票给他
hey, if you're for him, i'll throw the guy a vote. what the hell.
这次你投给谁?
who'd you vote for this time?
你是说布什还是某个人?
what? you mean bush and what's-his-name?
克里
kerry.
你不投给总统?
you didn't vote for president?
我考虑过 你知道么...
i thought about it, yeah, and, you know...
布什有点太头脑发热了
bush seemed way over his head, i know...
但无论如何在马里兰他不会赢的
but he wasn't gonna win in maryland, anyhow.
还有 这些人 选了谁都不重要
besides, these guys, it doesn't matter who you got.
没人知道真正发生了什么
none of them has a clue what's really going on.
我每天工作的地方
i mean, where i'm working every day...
是西巴尔的摩 要想他们知道那地方
the only way any of these guys is even gonna find west baltimore is if...
除非有次空军返回Andrews时 坠地撞入Monroe街
i dunno, air force one crash-lands into monroe street...on its way back to andrews.
完全就是毫无关系的
it just never connects.
起码我是这么认为的
not to what i see, anyway.
不过 这只是个人意见
hey, that's just me, though.
Colvin说 他想把那男孩关起来
the man colvin say he want the boy locked up...
要么明天就关闭自由区
or the free zone shuts down tomorrow.
对Hamsterdam的一切承诺也失效
all she wrote for hamsterdam.
Colvin?
colvin?
来自西区的
from the western.
Sham 那小孩是谁?
sham, who is this kid, man?
Tuckie那边的孩子
some young boy from tuckie's crew.
他关系强么?是谁的亲戚不?
he connected? kin to anybody?
不是 他只是来了几个月
no, he only been on for a couple months or so.
他干嘛杀人?
what he use the whistle for?
有些Ghost Kane那边的黑鬼嘲笑他的鞋子
some nigga in one of ghost kane crews laughed at his shoes.
交人
do it.
我去去就回
i'll be out in a minute.
不 他得把那些放到部门邮件里去
no, he needs to put those in the departmental mail.
对
yeah.
什么事?
what do you need?
自首
to turn myself in.
犯了什么事?
for what?
我开枪杀了一男孩
i shot a boy.
噢 是吗?
oh, yeah?